LUCA CARROZZO

9 Moore Park Rd 2021 Paddington Sydney, New South Wales Mob. 0452 147 586

Email: carrozzo.lc@gmail.com Portfolio: www.wpfriendly.it/portfolio

I would like to apply for a position as front end web developer. With 5 years of hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I am confident I will be an excellent addition to your organization.

Work Experience

01 July - 31 August 2018 Front End Developer / Web Developer Hoselink - Retail - Sydney (Australia)

Collaboration in project team:

- Developed design system following new front end development updates.
- Provide develop, implement a business-critical Neto ecommerce website using best practice approaches.

19 March - 19 June 2018 Front End Developer / WordPress Developer Infomedia Ltd - Computer Software - Sydney (Australia)

Collaboration in project team:

- Design, develop, implement a business-critical WordPress platform using best practice approaches;
- Provide WordPress and site design expertise including hands on execution of tasks required to implement the platform.

9 - 19 January 2018 Digital Designer / Front End Developer BMF - Marketing and Advertising - Sydney (Australia)

Collaboration as a Digital Designer / Front End Developer in digital team:

- Creating user flows, wireframes and visual mockups;
- Website development and production.

2015 - 2017 Front End Developer Iaki - Brand Engagement - Milano (Italy)

Collaboration as a Front End Developer in development teams on various projects, including:

- Website development <u>Tupassi.it</u>
- Bug-fixing front-end <u>Bormiolirocco.com</u>
- Front end development (Angular Js Ionic framework) for mobile app Il Libraio
- Promotional mini-site front-end development for <u>Lego Duplo</u>
- Front-end development restyling <u>agency site Iaki.it</u>

September 2014 - September 2015 Web Developer Koinomia - Creative Lab & Consulting - Martano - LE (Italy)

Web developer for the development of the following projects:

- Koinomia.it
- Meditcult.com
- Slowactivetours.com
- Alloggisalento.com

February 2012 - Present Front End Developer - Web Developer/Designer Freelance

Website development for companies and private clients in various sectors.

Latest projects:

- Wpfriendly.it Portfolio Online
- <u>limitlesskitetours.com</u> Australian client
- Tourango.it
- thebarraq.com
- Liberrera.it

Education

2014

Course in Social Media Marketing Marketing - Communication Web 2.0 - Social Media

Learning the basics to project and manage marketing campaigns, web communications and social media strategies, check and verify the corporate brand reputation, create content for the web 2.0 and business blogs.

November 2011 – May 2012 JTO training - Web designer 2.0 and multimedia communication - Italy Course in web designer 2.0 and multimedia communication

Learning of the realization of the digital graphic layout for the web online implementation through multilanguages and tecnologies

Key Competencies and Skills

Web Design:

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Web layout graphic development

Web Development:

- HTML5 + CSS3, XHTML + CSS
- CSS Preprocessing: SASS / LESS
- Responsive Design (framework Bootstrap)

- Automation Tools: Gulp.js
- Version Control: Gitlab
- PHP + MySQL
- JavaScript / jQuery
- Wordpress advanced knowledge
- Angular js (6 months project: Front end development for an Hybrid application)

Personal Skills

Languages:

• English: simple conversation, reading, and writing

French: fluent oral and writtenItalian: fluent oral and written